[{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"a", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"b", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"a", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"d", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"c", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"d", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"b", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"b", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"d", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"c", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"a", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"a", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"b", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"a", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"d", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"c", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"d", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"b", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"b", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"d", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"c", 
    "topic":"modern"
},
{
    "question":"choose one option",
    "options":["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    "answer":"a", 
    "topic":"modern"
},



{
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "68483590b1748fb6f2cf1b05"
    },
    "title": "sample-test-1",
    "start": {
      "$date": "2025-06-10T15:00:00.000Z"
    },
    "end": {
      "$date": "2025-06-10T15:30:00.000Z"
    },
    "topics": [
      "old"
    ],
    "questions": {
      "old": [
        {
          "$oid": "6846a41c35bdbc8299283b3f"
        },
        {
          "$oid": "6846a41c35bdbc8299283b40"
        },
        {
          "$oid": "6846a41c35bdbc8299283b4c"
        },
        {
          "$oid": "6846a41c35bdbc8299283b51"
        },
        {
          "$oid": "6846a41c35bdbc8299283b53"
        }
      ]
    },
    "answers": [
      "a",
      "b",
      "a",
      "b",
      "c"
    ],
    "records": []
  }
,


{
    "_id": {
      "$oid": "684c38ba60690f7ee268ba50"
    },
    "title": "sample1",
    "start": {
      "$date": "2025-06-13T14:39:26.000Z"
    },
    "end": {
      "$date": "2025-06-13T14:39:26.000Z"
    },
    "topics": [
      {
        "_id": "684a642284d2d35fee911b58",
        "topic": "old",
        "no_of_questions": 5
      },
      {
        "_id": "684a643a84d2d35fee911b59",
        "topic": "new",
        "no_of_questions": 5
      }
    ],
    "questions": [
      {
        "topic": "old",
        "questions": [
          {
            "$oid": "6846a41c35bdbc8299283b43"
          },
          {
            "$oid": "6846a41c35bdbc8299283b4c"
          },
          {
            "$oid": "6846a41c35bdbc8299283b54"
          },
          {
            "$oid": "6846a41c35bdbc8299283b4e"
          },
          {
            "$oid": "6846a41c35bdbc8299283b41"
          }
        ],
        "answers": [
          "c",
          "a",
          "a",
          "c",
          "a"
        ]
      },
      {
        "topic": "new",
        "questions": [
          {
            "$oid": "684482a5075a2765c4ef2522"
          },
          {
            "$oid": "684482a5075a2765c4ef2513"
          },
          {
            "$oid": "684482a5075a2765c4ef2518"
          },
          {
            "$oid": "684482a5075a2765c4ef2516"
          },
          {
            "$oid": "684482a5075a2765c4ef250f"
          }
        ],
        "answers": [
          "c",
          "d",
          "a",
          "d",
          "b"
        ]
      }
    ]
  },

{
    "msg ":"schema",
    "$jsonSchema": {
      "bsonType": "object",
      "required": [
        "_id",
        "title",
        "start",
        "end",
        "duration",
        "topics",
        "questions"
      ],
      "properties": {
        "_id": {
          "bsonType": "objectId"
        },
        "title": {
          "bsonType": "string"
        },
        "start": {
          "bsonType": "date"
        },
        "end": {
          "bsonType": "date"
        },
        "duration": {
          "bsonType": "int"
        },
        "topics": {
          "bsonType": "array",
          "items": {
            "bsonType": "object",
            "properties": {
              "_id": {
                "bsonType": "objectId"
              },
              "no_of_questions": {
                "bsonType": "int"
              },
              "topic": {
                "bsonType": "string"
              }
            },
            "required": [
              "_id",
              "no_of_questions",
              "topic"
            ]
          }
        },   
        "questions": {
          "bsonType": "array",
          "items": {
            "bsonType": "object",
            "properties": {
              "topic": {
                "bsonType": "string"
              },
              "questions": {
                "bsonType": "array",
                "items": {
                  "bsonType": "objectId"
                }
              },
              "answers": {
                "bsonType": "array",
                "items": {
                  "bsonType": "string"
                }
              }
            },
            "required": [
              "answers",
              "questions",
              "topic"
            ]
          }
        }
      }
    }
  }]
